Guide to the Office of Alumni Relations records, 1848-2005 RG0026
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Yearbooks and memorabilia, 1898-1995; RG0026 Series 16; 15 Linear feet (Box 1, Box 2, Box 3, Box 4, Box 5, Box 6, Box 7, Box 8, Box 9, Box 10, Box 11, Box 12, Box 13, Box 14)
  - Mounted photographs: "Mrs Kennedy and the two children watching at the President's body was taken from the White House", undated (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Mounted photographs: Building a snowman, ice-covered building; on campus?, undated (Box 9, Folder 6)
    3 photographs
  - Mounted photographs: "Snow Envelopes a City Campus", undated (Box 9, Folder 7)
    2 photographs
  - Mounted photographs: Woman being congratulated after receiving an award?, undated (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Mounted photographs: Workers protesting outside of the Department of Labor during the Vietnam War, undated (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Mounted photographs: Woman studying at bar of diner, undated (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Mounted photographs: Equipment for the band Derek and the Dominos, undated (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Mounted photographs: Student speaks to rally inside MC?, 1960 ca. (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Mounted photographs: Students outside the Circle Theater, undated (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Framed items: Ink drawing--street in DC, 1970 ca. (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Framed items: Ground plan--GW campus between 24th and 23rd street, including Ross Hall and the Himmelfarb Library, undated (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Framed items: Photograph--Marvin Center from 21st St., undated (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Framed items: Overhead reproduction of drawing--The Lawn (Quad) at GW, undated (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Framed items: Plaque, 03/26/1990 (Box 11, Folder 1)
    Northern Virginia Alumnae of Sigma Kappa Sorority in Memory of Lois Smith Simpson Morgenroth, 1st Woman President of the Student Council of GW 1945. Presented March 26 1990
  - Framed items: Ink drawing--Woodhull House presented to UPD by Office of Alumni Relations, undated (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Framed items: Aerial photographs--Commencement on the Ellipse, undated (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Framed items: Ink drawing--Woodhull House, undated (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Framed items: Seal of the Columbian College, adopted by the Board of Trustees in 1821, undated (Box 12, Folder 1)
    2 items
  - Framed items: Ink drawing--Lenthall Houses, undated (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Framed items: Pencil drawing--Marvin Center and Betts Theater from 21st St., undated (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Framed items: Example of GW Bachelor's degree, undated (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Framed items: Floor plan--Alumni House, 714 21st St. NW, 06/01/1979 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - GWU Alumni Achievement Award Design No.1, 1992 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - GWU Flag, undated (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - GWU Homecoming Banner, 1995 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Trophy--Homecoming float, undated (Box 14, Folder 4)
    Kept in trophy section of President's Room storage annex
- Alumni association files, 1923-1994; RG0026 Series 17; 10.5 Linear feet
  This series consists of general alumni association files, including executive committee meetings and minutes, governing board meetings, distinguished alumni achievement awards, alumni service awards, etc. The materials range in date from 1923-94, and were transferred to University Archives in 1999.
  - Executive Committee Meeting, 01/07/1992 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Executive Committee Meeting, 10/08/1991 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Executive Committee Meeting, 05/07/1991 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Executive Committee Meeting, 03/13/1991 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Executive Committee Meeting, 01/08/1991 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Executive Committee Meeting, 10/02/1990 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Executive Committee Meeting, 05/08/1990 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Executive Committee Meeting, 03/06/1990 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Executive Committee Meeting, 01/09/1990 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Executive Committee Meeting, 10/10/1989 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Executive Committee Meeting, 09/12/1989 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Executive Committee Meeting, 08/16/1989 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Executive Committee Meeting, 05/09/1989 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Executive Committee Meeting, 03/07/1989 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Executive Committee Meeting, 01/11/1989 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Executive Committee Meeting, 10/11/1988 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Executive Committee Meeting, 05/10/1988 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Executive Committee Meeting, 03/08/1988 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Executive Committee Meeting, 01/12/1988 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Executive Committee Meeting, 10/06/1987 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Executive Committee Meeting, 05/12/1987 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Executive Committee Meeting, 03/12/1987 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Executive Committee Meeting, 01/07/1987 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Executive Committee Meeting, 10/07/1986 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Executive Committee Meeting, 05/06/1986 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Executive Committee Meeting, 03/11/1986 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Executive Committee Meeting, 01/07/1986 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Executive Committee Meeting, 10/08/1985 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Executive Committee Meeting, 05/07/1985 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Executive Committee Meeting, 03/12/1985 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Executive Committee Meeting, 01/09/1985 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Executive Committee Meeting, 10/09/1984 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Executive Committee Meeting, 05/08/1984 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Executive Committee Meeting, 02/27/1984 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Executive Committee Meeting, 01/10/1984 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Executive Committee Meeting, 10/11/1983 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Executive Committee Meeting, 05/10/1983 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Executive Committee Meeting, 03/08/1983 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Executive Committee Meeting, 01/11/1983 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Executive Committee Meeting, 09/09/1982 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Executive Committee Meeting, 06/22/1982 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Executive Committee Meeting, 05/09/1982 (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Executive Committee Meeting, 09/29/1981 (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Executive Committee Meeting, 05/07/1981 (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - Executive Committee Meeting, 02/24/1981 (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - Executive Committee Meeting, 12/16/1980 (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - Executive Committee Meeting, 09/25/1980 (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - Executive Committee Meeting, 04/15/1980 (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - Executive Committee Meeting, 02/04/1980 (Box 1, Folder 49)
  - Executive Committee Meeting, 09/11/1979 (Box 1, Folder 50)
  - Executive Committee Meeting, 11/13/1979 (Box 1, Folder 51)
  - Executive Committee Meeting, 04/10/1979 (Box 1, Folder 52)
  - Executive Committee Meeting, 02/20/1979 (Box 1, Folder 53)
  - Executive Committee Meeting, 12/12/1978 (Box 1, Folder 54)
  - Executive Committee File, 1978-1980 (Box 1, Folder 55)
  - Executive Committee File, 1976-1978 (Box 1, Folder 56)
  - Executive Committee File, 1973-1974 (Box 1, Folder 57)
  - Executive Committee File, 1972-1973 (Box 1, Folder 58)
  - Executive Committee Minutes, 01/1940 --10/1942 (Box 1, Folder 59)
  - Executive Committee Minutes, 01/1938 --12/1939 (Box 1, Folder 60)
  - Executive Committee Minutes, 1942-1949 (Box 1, Folder 61)
  - Executive Committee Minutes, 01/1936 --11/1937 (Box 1, Folder 62)
  - Executive Committee Minutes, 01/1933 --12/1935 (Box 1, Folder 63)
  - Executive Committee Minutes, 1928-1933 (Box 1, Folder 64)
  - Executive Committee Minutes, 1923-1927 (Box 1, Folder 65)
  - Governing Board Meetings, 10/15/1991 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Governing Board Meetings, 05/15/1991 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Governing Board Meetings, 03/20/1991 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Governing Board Meetings, 01/23/1991 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Governing Board Meetings, 10/10/1990 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Governing Board Meetings - Biennial Meeting, 06/27/1990 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Governing Board Meetings, 05/16/1990 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Governing Board Meetings, 03/14/1990 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Governing Board Meetings, 01/17/1990 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Governing Board Meetings, 10/08/1989 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Governing Board Meetings - Annual Meeting, 06/1989 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Governing Board Meetings, 05/17/1989 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Governing Board Meetings, 01/18/1989 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Governing Board Meetings, 03/15/1989 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Governing Board Meetings, 10/19/1988 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Governing Board Meetings - Biennial Meeting, 01/29/1988 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Governing Board Meetings, 05/18/1988 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Governing Board Meetings, 03/16/1988 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Governing Board Meetings, 01/20/1988 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Governing Board Meetings, 10/14/1987 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Governing Board Meetings, 05/20/1987 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Governing Board Meetings, 03/18/1987 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Governing Board Meetings, 01/04/1987 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Governing Board Meetings, 10/15/1986 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Governing Board Meetings, 09/17/1986 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Governing Board Meetings - Biennial Meeting, 06/25/1986 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Governing Board Meetings - Election Meeting, 1986-1988 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Governing Board Meetings, 05/14/1986 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Governing Board Meetings, 03/19/1986 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Governing Board Meetings, 01/15/1986 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Governing Board Meetings, 10/16/1985 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Governing Board Meetings, 05/15/1985 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Governing Board Meetings, 03/20/1985 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Governing Board Meetings, 01/16/1985 (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Governing Board Meetings, 10/17/1984 (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Governing Board Meetings, 09/17/1984 (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - Governing Board Meetings - Election Meeting, 06/17/1984 (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - Governing Board Meetings, 03/14/1984 (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - Governing Board Meetings, 01/18/1984 (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - Governing Board Meetings, 10/18/1983 (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - Governing Board Meetings, 05/18/1983 (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - Governing Board Meetings, 03/16/1983 (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - Governing Board Meetings, 01/19/1983 (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - Governing Board Meetings, 10/20/1982 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Governing Board Meetings, 07/14/1982 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Governing Board Meetings, 03/17/1982 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Governing Board Meetings, 01/20/1982 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Governing Board Meetings, 10/14/1981 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Governing Board Meetings, 07/15/1981 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Governing Board Meetings, 05/20/1981 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Governing Board Meetings, 03/18/1981 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Governing Board Meetings, 01/14/1981 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Governing Board Meetings, 10/15/1980 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Governing Board Meetings, 01/16/1980 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Governing Board Meetings, 03/19/1980 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Governing Board Meetings, 10/17/1979 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Governing Board Meetings, 05/16/1979 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Governing Board Meetings, 03/14/1979 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Governing Board Meetings, 01/17/1979 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Governing Board Meetings, 10/18/1978 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Governing Board Directory & Biographical Information, 1978-1980 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Governing Board Nominations, 1978-1980 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Governing Board File, 1978-1979 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Governing Board File, 1977-1978 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Governing Board Nominees, 1976-1978 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Governing Board File, 1979-1980 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Governing Board File, 1980-1981 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Governing Board Directory, 1979-1980 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Governing Board Directory, 1982-1984 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Governing Board Election, 1978-1980 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Governing Board File, 1976-1977 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Governing Board File, 1975-1976 (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Governing Board Directory, 1975-1976 (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - Governing Board Directory, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - Governing Board File, 1974-1975 (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - Governing Board File, 1973-1974 (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - Governing Board File, 1973 (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - Governing Board File, 1972-1973 (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - Governing Board File, 1974-1976 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Governing Board Minutes, 1975-1976 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Governing Board Minutes, 1974-1975 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Governing Board Minutes, 1972-1973 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Governing Board Minutes, 01/1970 --01/1972 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Governing Board Minutes, 05/1968 --05/1969 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Governing Board Minutes, 02/1967 --02/1968 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Governing Board Minutes, 12/1965 --02/1968 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Confidential Files, undated (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Alumni Trustees, 1989 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Alumni Trustees, 1988 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Alumni Trustees, 1987 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Alumni Trustees, 1985 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Alumni Trustees, 1983-1984 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Alumni Trustees, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Alumni Trustees, 1981 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Alumni Trustees, 1977 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Alumni Trustees, 1975-1976 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Alumni Trustees, 1973-1974 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Alumni Trustees, 1972-1973 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - University & Alumni Trustee File, undated (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Governing Board - General, 1990-1992 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Governing Board Committees, 1990-1992 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Trustee Committee, 1990-1992 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Nominating Committee, 1990-1992 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Alumni Service Award Committee, 1990-1992 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Regional Programs Committee, 1990-1992 (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Reunion/Local Programs Committee, 1990-1992 (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - Alumni Achievement Awards Committee, 1990-1992 (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - By-laws Committee, 1990-1992 (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - Finance Committee, 1990-1992 (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - Alumni Achievement Awards, 1979 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Alumni Achievement Awards Nominations, 1977-1978 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Alumni Achievement Awards Nominations, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Alumni Achievement Awards, 1976-1977 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Alumni Achievement Awards Nominations, 1974-1975 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Alumni Achievement Awards Nominations, 1973-1974 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Alumni Achievement Awards Nominations, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Alumni Achievement Awards, 1973-1974 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Alumni Achievement Awards Nominations, 1972-1973 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Alumni Achievement Awards Nominations, 1971-1972 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Alumni Achievement Awards Nominations, 1972 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Alumni Achievement Awards, 1970-1971 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Alumni Achievement Awards Correspondence, 02/1970 --06/1970 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Awards Samples, undated (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Alumni Achievement Awards Correspondence, 1969 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Alumni Achievement Awards Correspondence, 02/1968 --06/1968 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Alumni Achievement Awards, 1968-1969 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Alumni Achievement Awards, undated (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Centennial Convocation, Law School, 10/12/1965 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Awards Program & Dinner, 05/20/1965 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Awards Criteria and Procedures, undated (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Alumni Achievement Awards, 1966-1967 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Alumni Achievement Awards Correspondence, 02/1967 --06/1967 (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Awards Program & Dinner, 05/17/1969 (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Awards Program & Dinner, 05/17/1968 (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Awards Program & Dinner Copies, 06/02/1967 (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - Awards Program & Dinner, 06/03/1966 (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - Alumni Service Awards, 1992 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Community Service Awards, 1992 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Volunteer Service Awards, 1992 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Community Service Awards, 1991 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Alumni Service Awards, 1991 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - GAA New Service/Achievement Awards, 1991 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Alumni Service & Community Service Awards, 1990 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Community Service Awards, 1990 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Alumni Service Awards, 1989 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Alumni Service Awards, 1988 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Alumni Service Awards, 1987 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Alumni Service Awards, 1986 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Alumni Service Awards, 1985 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Alumni Service Awards, 1984 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Alumni Service Awards, 1983 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Alumni Service Awards, 1982 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Alumni Service Awards, 1981 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Alumni Service Awards, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Alumni Service Awards, 1979 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Alumni Service Awards, 1977-1978 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Alumni Service Awards, 1976-1977 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Alumni Service Awards, 1975-1976 (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - Alumni Service Awards - Special Reception For Past Recipients, 02/20/1978 (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - Alumni Service Awards Nominations, 1975 (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - Alumni Service Awards, 1975 (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - Alumni Service Awards, 1974 (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - Alumni Service Awards, 1974-1975 (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - Alumni Service Awards, 1973 (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - Alumni Service Awards, 1967-1972 (Box 6, Folder 29)
  - Alumni Service Awards correspondence to, 1969 (Box 6, Folder 30)
  - Alumni Service Awards Criteria and Procedures, undated (Box 6, Folder 31)
  - Alumni Service Awards, 1993 (Box 6, Folder 32)
  - Community Service Awards, 1993 (Box 6, Folder 33)
  - Volunteer Service Awards, 1993 (Box 6, Folder 34)
  - GAA Committees, undated (Box 6, Folder 35)
  - Alumni Service and Community Service Awards Committee, 1992-1994 (Box 6, Folder 36)
  - Public Relations Committee, 1992-1994 (Box 6, Folder 37)
  - By-laws Committee, 1992-1994 (Box 6, Folder 38)
  - Distinguished Alumni Achievement Awards Committee, 1992-1994 (Box 6, Folder 39)
  - Finance Committee, 1992-1994 (Box 6, Folder 40)
  - Homecoming Committee, 1992-1994 (Box 6, Folder 41)
  - Nominating Committee, 1992-1994 (Box 6, Folder 42)
  - Trustee Recommendation Committee, 1992-1994 (Box 6, Folder 43)
  - Reunion Committee, 1992-1994 (Box 6, Folder 44)
  - Distinguished Alumni Achievement Awards, 1991 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Distinguished Alumni Achievement Awards, 1990 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Distinguished Alumni Achievement Awards, 1989 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Distinguished Alumni Achievement Awards, 1988 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Distinguished Alumni Achievement Awards, 1986 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Distinguished Alumni Achievement Awards, 1985 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Distinguished Alumni Achievement Awards, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Distinguished Alumni Achievement Awards, 1982 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Distinguished Alumni Achievement Awards, 1981 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Distinguished Alumni Achievement Awards, 1980 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Ballots - Governing Board, 1974-1976 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Ballots Correspondence, 1968 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Ballots - General Alumni Association, 1966-1968 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Banquet - Joint Medical & GAA, 02/21/1959 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - GAA Governing Board Biennial Meeting, 05/1976 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - GAA Governing Board Biennial Meeting, 05/1974 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - GAA Governing Board Biennial Meeting, 05/1978 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - DAAA Book Project - Photo, undated (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Service Awards Committee (Governing Board), 1984-1986 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Committees - GAA Governing Board, 1982-1984 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Achievement Awards Committee, 1982-1984 (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Finance Committee, 1984-1986 (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - Finance Committee, 1982-1984 (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - Regional Alumni Programs Committee, 1982-1984 (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - Committee on Objectives & Programs, 1981-1982 (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - Awards Committee - GAA Governing Board, 1980-1982 (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - Trustee Recommendation Committee (GB), 1986-1988 (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - Finance Committee, 1986-1988 (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - Reunion/Local Programs Committee, 1986-1988 (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - Regional Programs Committee, 1986-1988 (Box 7, Folder 30)
  - Public Relations Committee, 1986-1988 (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - Distinguished Alumni Achievement Awards Committee, 1986-1988 (Box 7, Folder 32)
  - Alumni Service Awards Committee, 1986-1988 (Box 7, Folder 33)
  - Committees - Governing Board (GAA), 1984-1986 (Box 7, Folder 34)
  - Distinguished Alumni Achievement Awards Committee, 1984-1986 (Box 7, Folder 35)
  - Public Relations Committee, 1984-1986 (Box 7, Folder 36)
  - Reunion Committee, 1984-1986 (Box 7, Folder 37)
  - Regional Programs Committee, 1984-1986 (Box 7, Folder 38)
  - Trustee Recommendation Committee, 1984-1986 (Box 7, Folder 39)
  - Alumni Service Awards Committee, 1983 (Box 7, Folder 40)
  - Spring Commencement - Medical School, 05/25/1979 (Box 7, Folder 41)
  - Spring Commencement - Columbian School, 05/06/1979 (Box 7, Folder 42)
- Alumni weekend, 1997; RG0026 Series 18; 0.5 Linear feet (Box 1)
  This series consists of two folders of participants for the 50th anniversary class reunion, and a t-shirt for the 1997 alumni weekend. The materials date from 1997 and were transferred to University Archives in 1998.
- Notebook, 1959-1964; RG0026 Series 20; 0.5 Linear feet (Flat box 1)
  This series consists of one notebook containing GW publications cover proposals. The materials range in date from 1959-64, and were transferred to University Archives in 1987.
- Alumni files, 1889-2005; RG0026 Series 21; 2 Linear feet (Box 1, Box 2)
  This series includes such topics as histories, activities, brochures, biographies, events, awards, senior class celebration announcements and the booklet "Hamburg the Colonial Town that became the seat of The George Washington University".
  - Alumni - course audit program, 1977-1996 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Alumni - Distinguished Alumni Achievement Awards, 1970-1997 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Alumni - Distinguished Alumni lists, 1940-1996 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Alumni - Externship Program, undated (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Alumni - fundraising, undated (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Alumni - General Alumni Association, 1950-1994 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Alumni - Homecoming, 1937-1998 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Alumni - Alumni Association, 1984-2005 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Alumni - Alumni Association - Columbian College/School of Arts and Sciences, 1989-1996 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Alumni - Alumni Association - Pre-1900 History, 1889-1890 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Alumni - Alumni Club, 1991-1995 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Alumni - Alumni Club - George Washington University New York Alumni - "Minute Men" - Correspondence of George Pollard, President of Minute Men, 1938-1941 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Alumni - Alumni Club - "Minute Men", 1923-1937 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Alumni - Alumni Club - "Minute Men", 1937-1940 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Alumni - Alumni Club - Minute Men 1938-1954 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Alumni - Alumni Club - Minute Men, 1941-1943 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Alumni - Alumni Club - Minute Men, 1954-1956 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Alumni - Alumni College, 1982-1997 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Alumni - Alumni Relations Office, 1979-1992 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Alumni - Alumni Reunion Weekend, 1980-1990 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Alumni - Alumni Reunion Weekend, 1991-1994 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Alumni - Alumni Reunion Weekend, 1995-2004 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Alumni - Awards Dinners, 1972-2000 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Alumni - Biographical Information/Individuals, 1947-1996 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Alumni - Biographical Information - Individuals appearing on the cover of Time magazine, 1983-1974 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Alumni - Calendars, 1965-1991 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Alumni - Colonials, Inc., 1973-1985 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Alumni - special events, 1941-1996 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Alumni - special events - lectures, 1944-1997 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Alumni - special events - travel tours, 1981-1992 (Box 2, Folder 23)